vitalydesign.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy – Vitaly

The services on this site are offered to you by VITALY DESIGN Ltd., parent company of Vitaly. For the rest of this text, Vitaly Design will be used, but it is understood that Vitaly is a part of VITALY DESIGN Ltd.  

Vitaly knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we’ll do so reasonably and safely. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Vitaly, you’re accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. You can browse our site without revealing who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in North America. We are hosted by Shopify and therefore, cannot know the exact physical location of each and every single server.

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Vitaly Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Vitaly. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information You Give Us** : We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you, but we respect your privacy when we market our products and services.

**Automatic Information** : We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Vitaly.

Certain information, although convenient for identification, is voluntary. It is up to you whether you want to provide this or other suitable identification, subject to any legal requirements.

We collect, use and disclose personal information only for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances.

**How Does Vitaly Handle Cookies?**

Cookies are small files that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser, to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as personalized greetings, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

The "help" or “settings” section of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Vitaly’s essential features, we recommend you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to checkout, or use any Vitaly products and services that require you to sign in.

**Third-Party Data Collection Technology**

We use third-party, interest-based advertising services to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These third-party services display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online. We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our website, this information is used to serve ads for our products and services when you visit this website or other websites. These third-party services use non-personally identifiable information (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, device and platform information, cookie and session IDs) and personally identifiable information (such as an IP address) during your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services believed to be of greater interest to you. These services typically collect this information using a cookie or a third party web beacon or clear gif. We do not currently respond to or process do no track signals from web browsers.

**Does Vitaly Share The Information It Receives**?

Information about our customers is a key part of our business, and we’re not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below.

**Third-Party Service Providers** : We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf but, we do not sell to third parties any Personal Information. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Business Transfers** : As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Vitaly or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information of course will be one of the transferred assets.

**Protection of Vitaly and Others** : We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Vitaly, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit-risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

**With Your Consent** : Other than as set out above, you’ll receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you’ll have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you enter.

It’s important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. Be sure to sign off when you’ve finished using a shared computer. 

As discussed above, you always can choose not to provide information, although it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of additional Vitaly features.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as your personal account information and profile. 

If you don’t want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please email us so we can further assist you. (If you don’t want to receive Terms and Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of Vitaly, and it’s your responsibility to review them for changes.)

We keep the personal information we collect about you strictly confidential. Only authorized personnel have access to this personal information.

**What About Third-Party Advertisers And Links To Other Web Sites?**

Our site may include third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites.

These third-party Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our Web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection.

**Which Information Can I Access?**

Vitaly gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Vitaly for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.

**Are Children Allowed To Use Vitaly?**

If you’re under 18, you may use Vitaly only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

If you choose to visit Vitaly, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, settlement of disputes, and application of the law of Canada. If you have any concern about privacy at Vitaly, please contact us, and we’ll try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Terms and Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

**Related Practices And Information**

See Terms & Conditions of Use.

**Examples Of Information Collected**

**Information You Give Us:** You provide most such information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; make an order; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one, if you’ve used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; and provide and rate reviews, when applicable. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and telephone number; credit card information; names of people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and telephone number; content of reviews and e-mails to us; and financial information.

You may withdraw, verify accuracy or change some information you give us at any time, provided there are no legal requirements to prevent this, by sending an e-mail to info@vitalydesign.com.

**Automatic Information:** Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; geographic location, computer and connection information, such as browser type, version and timezone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features such as “Popular Products” Lists; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the telephone number used to call our customer service number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Website for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**Information From Other Sources:** Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

**Information You Can Access:** Examples of information you can currently access easily at Vitaly include up-to-date information regarding recent orders, personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, communications preferences), payment settings (including credit card information, gift certificate, gift card, and check balances) and recommendations.

**Requests, Questions or Comments**

If you have questions or inquiries relating to our privacy practices or procedures, or want to make a request concerning your personal information, please write to Vitaly’s Privacy Officer/Data Protection Officer at the address provided below: 

Vitaly Design Ltd.

1020 Islington Ave.

[Unit# 9B](https://maps.google.com/?q=1020%0D+Islington+Ave.%0D+%0D+Unit%23+9B&entry=gmail&source=g)\- Dock 3&4

Etobicoke, ON

M8Z6A4

Canada 

Attention: Privacy Officer/Data Protection Officer

If you remain unhappy with a response you receive about the treatment of your personal information, you can also refer your concerns to the relevant privacy or data protection supervisor in your jurisdiction.
